ILGWU Local 62 Correspondence 5780/022
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series Series II: Louis Stulberg correspondence, 1947-1956.
  - General Correspondence. I.L.G.W.U. Training Institute, 1957-1962 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - General Correspondence. I.L.G.W.U. Union Label Dept., 1958-1961 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - General Correspondence. I.L.G.W.U. Upper South Dept., 1956-1961 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - General Correspondence. I.L.G.W.U. Welfare Funds Control Dept., 1960 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - General Correspondence. Impartial Chairman, 1934 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - General Correspondence. Installation of Officers, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    Contains congratulatory telegrams.
  - General Correspondence. Internal Revenue Service, 1943-1945 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    Contains correspondence. re tax of vacation fund payments.
  - General Correspondence. Italian-American Labor Council, United, 1961-1963 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - General Correspondence. Jewish Daily Forward, 1954-1962 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - General Correspondence. Jewish Labor Committee, 1954-1962 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    Incl. correspondence. re (World War II) children "adopted" by Local 62.
  - General Correspondence. Job referrals, 1934-1962 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - General Correspondence. Job requests, 1934 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - General Correspondence. Jurisdictional disputes, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    Dispute between Local 62, ILGWU and Local 238, International Union of Doll and Toy Workers. Incl. correspondence. between David Dubinsky and Wm. F. Schnitzler, Secretary-Treasurer, AFL-CIO.
  - General Correspondence. Labor Day parades, 1960-1961 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - General Correspondence. Lieberman, Elias, 1934 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    Corres. re wage claims by members against firms.
  - General Correspondence. Lieberman, Katz and Aronson, 1954-1961 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence. Membership figures, 1934-1958 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    Incl. dues information for 1956-58.
  - General Correspondence. Membership meetings, 1956-1963 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    Incl. agendas, resolutions, reports, installation of officers meeting.
  - General Correspondence. Miscellaneous correspondence, 1934-1962 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence. National Committee for Labor Israel, -(Histadrut), American Trade Union Council of the, 1957-1962 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    Incl. correspondence. and pictures of Histadrut Cultural Club in Moshava Kineret and Histadrut Centre in Beersheeba erected through Local 62 donations.
  - General Correspondence. National Foundation for Infantile Paralysis, 1954-1961 (Box 11, Folder 6-7)
  - General Correspondence. National Labor Relations Board, 1956-1962 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - General Correspondence. National Recovery Act, 1933-1934 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    Corres, re Undergarment Code and Undergarment arid Negligee Code Bulletin.
  - General Correspondence. Negotiating committees for labor contracts, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - General Correspondence. New York City, Welfare Dept. of, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - General Correspondence. New York State Federation of Labor, 1954-1958 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - General Correspondence. New York State Labor Relations Board, 1954-1955 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - General Correspondence. New York State Legislature, 1957-1960 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - General Correspondence. Office Employees International Union, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - General Correspondence. Political campaigns, 1954-1962 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - General Correspondence. Puerto Rico, Commonwealth of, Dept. of Labor, Migration Division, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    Corres. re members' complaints.
  - General Correspondence. R, 1954-1959 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    Incl. correspondence. w. Eleanor Roosevelt.
  - General Correspondence. Retirement Benefits Fund, 1954-1958 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    Incl. Rules and Regulations of the Local 62-Local 10 Retirement Benefits Fund.
  - General Correspondence. Retirement Benefits Fund, 1960-1963 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - General Correspondence. Retirement Benefits Fund, 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    Incl. Board of Trustees minutes, financial statements, report to Superintendent of Insurance, State of New York.
  - General Correspondence. S, 1934-1959 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - General Correspondence. Salary Schedules, Local 62 employees, 1954-1961 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - General Correspondence. Schneiderman, Rose, 1933 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - General Correspondence. Schoenholtz, Isidore, 1933-1963 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - General Correspondence. Schoenwald, Matthew, 1962-1963 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - General Correspondence. Schoenwald, Matthew, 1956-1962 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence. Severance Benefits Fund/severance pay, 1959-1961 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    Incl. minutes of the Board of Trustees, Rules and Regulations of the Local 62-Local 10 Severance Benefits Fund
  - General Correspondence. Shops, 1933-1960 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    Analyses of shops, 1954-60 and dues records, 1933-34.
  - General Correspondence. Shop chairladies, 1933-1962 (Box 12, Folder 4-5)
    Incl. correspondence., notices.
  - General Correspondence. Shop meetings, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 6-15)
  - General Correspondence. Shop meetings, 1933-1934 (Box 13, Folder 1-15)
  - General Correspondence. Socialist Party, 1934 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence. Strikes, 1933 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - General Correspondence. Stulberg, Louis, 1953-1962 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    Incl. Norman Thomas letter, correspondence. w. Robert F. Wagner Jr. and w. United Hatters, Cap and Millinery Workers' International Union re loan from ILGWU.
  - General Correspondence. Trade associations. Allied Underwear Association, 1946-1962 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence. Trade associations. The Lingerie Manufacturers Association, Inc. and the Negligee Manufacturers Association, Inc., 1933-1963 (Box 14, Folder 5-6)
  - General Correspondence. Trade associations. United Underwear Contractors Association, Inc., 1958-1963 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - General Correspondence. Trade associations. Undergarment Accessories Association, Inc., 1953-1954 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - General Correspondence. Trade associations, agreements with, 1921-1960 (Box 14, Folder 8-12)
    Incl. several agreements with individual firms.
  - General Correspondence. Trade associations, agreements with, 1960-1963 (Box 15, Folder 1-2)
  - General Correspondence. U.S. Tour, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence. Unity House, 1949-1959 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence. Voter registration drives, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence. Women's Trade Union League, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    Gerel Rubien, President.
  - General Correspondence. Yiddish Scientific Institute (YIVO), 1955 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Series Series III: Gerol Rubien files, 1921-1976
  - General Correspondence. Education, 1933-1975 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    Donated by Gerel Rubien.
  - General Correspondence. I.L.G.W.U. Management Engineering Dept., 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - General Correspondence. Medicare, oral history, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    Interview on Medicare with oral history research office, Columbia University. Donated by Gerel Rubien.
  - General Correspondence. Medicare/Social Security, 1961-1967 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    Incl. correspondence. re 1961 and 1963 trips to Florida. Donated by Gerel Rubien.
  - General Correspondence. Misc., 1923-1943 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    Incl. correspondence., Local 62 1925 election results. Donated by Gerel Rubien.
  - General Correspondence. Politics, 1965-1976 (Box 15, Folder 13-14)
  - General Correspondence. Truth-in-Lending Act, 1963-1968 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Scrapbook, 1933 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    Contains clippings on general strike
  - Scrapbook, 1933-1934 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    Contains clippings
  - Scrapbook, 1934-1935 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Scrapbook, 1913-1939 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Scrapbooks, 1937-1939 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Scrapbook, 1941 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    Contains clippings on Samuel Shore
  - Our Union, 1938-1968 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    Official publication of Local 62
  - Agreements, 1922-1966 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Brookwood, 1921-1929 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Certificates, 1929-1959 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, 1949-1968 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1924-1980 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Local 62, 1926-1967 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Local 62, 1938-1940 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    Minutes and decisions of the Sick Benefit and Relief Fund Committee
  - New York Women's Trade Union League, 1933-1949 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Group photograph, 1921 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Price lists and reports, 1934-1950 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Printed material, 1921-1949 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Rose Schneiderman, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    February
  - Speeches, 1922-1958 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    Delivered by Mary Goff Schuster and Samuel Shore
  - Labor Problems, 1938-1939 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    Radio talks by Samuel Shore
  - Speeches, 1942-1943 (Box 17, Folder 15)